他悠扬婉转的声音让所有人卸下心防 也没有人能够看穿歌声的出处
六个月前
你到底是怎么了
What the hell is the matter with you?
你怎么敢就这样跑开
Don't you dare run away from me.
请不要伤害我 求你了
Please, don't hurt me!
我告诉过你要穿黑色裙子
I told you to wear the black dress.
已经送洗了
It's at the cleaners!
而且 你喜欢这条裙子
Besides, you like this dress.
你总是说我穿着它有多么好看
You always said how good I looked in it.
黑色能将你衬托的更美
You look better in black.
我再戴点儿装饰
I'll put on something else.
这就是你的问题
That's your whole problem.
当我告诉你做什么的时候
When I tell you to do something,
你就该这样去做
you should just do it!
啊 不要打我
Aah! Don't hit me!
不要伤害我
Don't hurt me!
喔 老天爷
Oh, my God.
911报警中心
911.
你有什么紧急情况
What is your emergency?
是的 我们需要一辆救护车
Yes. We need an ambulance.
- 早安  - 嗨
- Morning. - Hey.
我想了想昨晚我们的谈话
So I... I've been thinking about what we talked about last night.
- 关于Juliette的  - 是
- Juliette? - Yeah.
我觉得你该带她去拖车看看
And I think that you should take her to the trailer.
难道你不觉得你才应该带她去吗
Don't you think you should be the one who...
不 现在你跟她处得更好
No, you're on better terms with her right now.
也许吧 但这是你们俩之间的事儿 而不是我和她的
Well, maybe, but isn't this more of a you-and-her thing than a me-and-her thing?
如果去房车能帮她恢复记忆
If going to the trailer helps bring back her memories,
她就有可能会想起所有的事儿
then there's a chance that she's gonna remember everything.
也可能会像第一次去那样糟
And it could go as badly as it did the first time.
但是如果你带她去
But if you take her to the trailer...
噢 我明白了
Oh, I get it.
所以如果我疯了就没什么大不了的
So if I'm crazy, no big deal.
我们总不会都疯了吧
Hey, well, we can't both be crazy.
为什么不会
Why not?
我的意思是 考虑到我们以她的立场谈过的事情
I mean, given what we're talking about,from her point of view.
这值得一试
It's worth a try.
要是她想起所有的事情怎么办
What if she does remember everything?
我是指 所有事情
I mean, everything.
那我怎么应付过去
How am I supposed to finagle that?
就做你该做的事儿
Just do whatever you have to do.
我知道这个要求有些过分
I know this is asking a lot,
但是Monroe 拜托了 就当是为了我
but, Monroe, please, for me.
多谢
Thank you.
毋庸置疑
And the people will prove beyond any doubt
十月十六日晚
that on the night of October 16th,
被告Donald Nidaria蓄谋杀害了
the defendant Donald Nidaria did willfully and with malice aforethought,
他新婚六个月的妻子Katherine
murder Katherine, his wife of only six months.
现在我们将听到被告的开庭陈述
We will now hear opening statements from the defense.
Kellogg先生 请
Mr. Kellogg.
陪审团的各位成员
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
六个月前 我的委托人Donald Nidaria
six months ago, my client Donald Nidaria
经历了一场难以想像的悲剧
suffered an unimaginable tragedy.
他挚爱的妻子Katherine
His beloved wife Katherine,
尽管他尽其所能为她提供极其需要的精神治疗
despite all his heroic efforts to provide her the psychiatric care she so badly needed,
还是屈服于她黑暗的本性
succumbed to the demons of her darker nature...
纠缠她多年的恶魔
demons that had been with her for so many years,
唆使她跳下卧室的阳台
driving her to commit suicide at their home
走向自杀
by leaping to her death from their bedroom balcony.
在这场悲剧中更加令人感到侮辱的是
To add insult to this terrible injury,
我的委托人被逮捕 错误地被指控为谋杀犯
my client was arrested and wrongfully charged with murder.
女士们 先生们
Murder, ladies and gentlemen,
被指控谋杀了他愿意为其付出生命的女子
of the woman he loved more than life itself.
- 你好  - 嗨 Juliette
- Hello? - Hey, Juliette.
我是Monroe
It's me, Monroe.
我一直在想着拖车的事情
I've been doing some thinking about the trailer, and...
我想也许我可以带你去
I think maybe I should take you,
我的意思是如果你仍然想去的话
I mean, if you still wanna go
并且你也不忙得话
and if you're not busy.
我是说你可能会很忙
I mean, you know, you could be busy.
Juliette 还在听吗
Juliette?
不 我仍然想去
No, I-I... I still wanna go.
什么时候
When?
现在就可以出发
I'm sort of ready right now.
- 好的  - 我是说就是现在
- Okay. - I mean, right now,
因为我正站在你房门前
as in I'm standing on your front porch.
如果这个能帮你恢复记忆
Look, if this is gonna help bring your memories back...
喔 好吧
oh, okay.
发生了什么
What's wrong?
没什么 我只是没想到你会这么做
Nothing. I just didn't think you'd do it.
真的吗 因为我
Really? Because I...
在改变主意前我们赶紧出发
we're going before anybody changes their mind.
好
Okay.
我完全记得来过这里
I totally remember being here.
当时天在下雨
It was raining.
你记得Nick陪着你吗
Do you remember Nick being with you?
没有 我只记得我当时很沮丧
No, I just remember being really upset.
你确定你想这么做
You sure you wanna do this?
恩
Yes.
有想起什么吗
Any bells ringing?
还没
Not yet.
好吧 慢慢想
Well, take your time.
不要强求
Don't force it.
你认识Marie姑妈吗
Did you know aunt Marie?
我在医院遇到过一次
I met her once in the hospital.
那可能是在她遇袭之后
That would've been after she was attacked.
你还记得那件事儿
So you remember that?
恩 我听到枪声跑出屋 看到她
Yeah, I heard the gunshots,and I ran outside, and I saw her...
看到她正躺在街上
saw her lying in the street.
怎么
What?
我就在这里见他
That's where I've been seeing him.
喔 天哪 我想起来了
Oh, my God. I remember him.
他坐在这张桌子前
He was sitting at this desk.
- 你记得Nick  - 是的 他
- You remember Nick? - Yes, he...
他正在找一些东西
he was looking for something,
但这都是Marie姑妈的书
but these are aunt Marie's books.
她在干什么
What was she doing?
她怎么会有这些东西
Why would she even have all this stuff?
这个问题问得好极了
That's a really good question,
呃
and, um,
也需要个好答案
it deserves a really good answer.
我想Marie姑妈是个收藏爱好者
I guess you could say aunt Marie was a bit of a collector.
这些画可真奇怪
These drawings are so weird.
你知道他们是什么吗
Do you know what they are?
看起来她像是对民间传说很感兴趣
Uh, well, it appears she was into some sort of,uh, folkish-lore.
你是指童话故事
You mean like fairy tales?
恩 当然
Yeah, sure.
你 你也可以这样想
You could... you could go there.
那里面有什么
What's in there?
也许是类似的东西吧
Probably just more of the same.
并不是
Not really.
哇哦 看看这些武器
Wow. Look at all the weapons.
她可真是个收藏家 是吧
She really was a hell of a collector, huh?
为什么把这些东西放在拖车里
Why put all of this stuff in a trailer
并且一直带着它到处走
and haul it around with you?
为什么Nick不把它们处理了
And why didn't Nick just get rid of it all?
可能就像是家传宝物之类的东西吧
It's probably just, like,a family heirloom sort of thing,
传了很多代
passed down over generations.
我觉得今天已经做得很不错了
Well, I think this was a terrific success.
你记得Nick曾经在这里
You remember Nick being here.
我觉得这也许是个恢复的起点
And I think this might be the beginning of the road to recovery.
你现在想要离开
W...whoa, whoa, whoa. You wanna leave?
是啊 怎么 你不想吗
Yeah. What, you don't?
这里有太多可看的
There is so much more to this.
你不会想读到太多可能不在这儿的东西
Now you don't wanna go reading too much into what might not be here.
那这些奇奇怪怪的小瓶子呢
What about all these weird little bottles?
里边有什么 什么是
What's in them? What's...?
Siegbarste礼物 这是什么
"Siegbarste gift." What's that?
可能只是某种香水吧
It's probably just some perfume.
我是说 上边写着 礼物 所以
I mean, it says "Gift," So...
不要打开
Don't...
噢
Oh!
我的老天爷 这绝不是个礼物
Oh, my God. That's no gift.
是啊 你也许该把它放回去
Yeah, you might wanna put that one back.
你看到这些书了吗
You see these books?
里面全是图画
They're filled with drawings
我的先祖和其他人画的 那些人
made by my ancestors and others who had...
- Juliette  - 有着相同的能力
- Juliette? - The same ability.
都是格林生物的图画
And the drawings are of wesen.
首先你要把它浸入到这个东西里边去 就在这边 这个Siegbarste毒药
First, you have to dip it in this stuff right here... siegbarste gift.
Gift在德语中是毒药的意思
"Gift" Means "Poison" In German
他们在进行着一次非法的战斗
they were running an illegal fighting ring...
- 你还好吗  - 角斗士的年代
- Are you okay? - Time of the gladiators.
用这些来战斗
Fighting with these.
古代的武器 看 这是
Ancient weapons. Look. This...
当它们穿过一种叫woge的东西时
When they go through something called the woge...
是一颗晨星
Is a morning star.
这里边还有一把来复枪
There's a rifle in here
射出特殊的子弹
that shoots special bullets...
Juliette 你怎么了
Juliette, what's wrong?
Juliette
Juliette?
发生了什么
What happened?
- 我不知道  - 你还好吧
- I don't know. - Are you okay?
应该还好吧
II think so.
我不得不问问
I'm a little afraid to ask,
你在里面到底看到了什么
but what exactly did you see in there?
我看到了Nick
I saw Nick...
也许我该说我看到了好多Nick
maybe I should say I saw nicks.
我看到他 到处都看到了
I saw him... Everywhere.
你在说什么 不止一个Nick
What do you mean? More than one?
是的 然后他们
Yes, and then they were...
他们都同时在说话
they were all talking at the same time.
我不明白他们任何一个人的话
And I didn't understand what any of them were saying.
好了 我们也许没有用对方法
Okay. We might not be doing this right.
我是说 记忆可能是有些微妙的
I mean, memories can be kinda tricky.
我的记忆就像是地狱一样
Mine sure as hell are.
我想回家了
I think I just want to go home.
好的
Okay.
Rosalee
Rosalee?
在这儿
Back here.
我原本打算在G.K.那边定个位子
I tried to get us a table at G.K.'s,
但他们不接受预订
but they won't take a reservation
除非你要开一个19人大派对
unless you're a party of, like, 19, so...
我今晚不是很想出去玩
I don't really feel like going out tonight.
怎么啦 你病了吗
What's the matter? You sick?
可能吧
I'm something.
我觉得你没发烧啊
Doesn't feel like you have a fever.
今天陪审团工作如何 你去了没
How was jury duty? Did you even go?
呃 我去了
Oh, I went.
大概进行到一半的时候
About halfway through,
我开始感到不大舒服
I started feeling not so good.
或许你应该请病假
Maybe you should call in sick.
反正他们有替补
I mean, they have alternates.
嗯 我会看看我明天感觉如何
Mm, I'll see how I feel tomorrow.
我觉得我只是
I think I'm just...
只是在生自己的气
I'm just mad at myself.
为啥 你做了什么吗
Why, what'd you do?
一开始 我是这样认为这个案子的
I started out feeling one way about the case,
然后我突然就有了完全相反的想法
and then I went completely in the other direction.
哇 看来那是个很厉害的律师啊
Wow. Sounds like someone's a hell of a lawyer.
也许吧
I guess.
在那儿的时候 我以为自己病了
But when I was there, I thought I was getting sick.
一离开那地方 就感觉好点了
Once I left, I started feeling better,
现在 我只是有点头痛
and now, I just have a headache.
要不你回家睡一觉吧
Why don't you go home and go to bed?
- 我来关门  - 嗯
- I'll close up. - Mm.
那再好不过了
I'd appreciate that.
嗯 谢谢
Mm, thank you.
你是最贴心的
You're the best.
嘿 我明天开车载你去法院好吗
Hey, how about I drive you to court tomorrow?
我很乐意 晚安
I'd like that. Night.
晚安
Night.
哇
Wow!
闻起来好棒
Smells good.
我不知道你还会烧菜诶
I didn't know you could cook.
呃 我不会烧 这是外卖
Oh, I, uh... I can't, this is take-out.
你现在不是应该和Rosalee你侬我侬吗
Weren't you supposed to be on a date with Rosalee?
是啊 但她身体不舒服 所以
Yeah, she didn't feel so good, so...
你在读什么
what are you reading?
信不信由你
Believe it or not,
我刚收到一封来自我妈妈的电子邮件
I think I just got an email from my mom.
不是吧
Seriously?
信上写了什么
What does it say?
"抱歉 这么久没联系你
"Sorry to be off the radar for so long.
"我想你 我一切都好
"I miss you. All is well.
"我会好好规划那笔钱的
"I plan to spend the money wisely.
爱你的 妈妈"
Love, mom."
这是暗号 对吗
That's code, right?
她是指那些硬币
She's talking about the coins.
哇
Wow.
嗯 我觉得这是件好事
Well, that's a good thing, I guess.
这让我想起 嗯
Which reminds me, um...
我带Juliette去拖车那边了
I took Juliette to the trailer.
然后呢
And?
实际上她记得在拖车里
She actually remembered seeing you
见过你
in the trailer.
她记得我
She remembered me?
只记得在拖车里的情景而已
Just in the trailer.
这是一个开端 对吧
Well, that's a start, right?
嗯 这的确是个开端
Oh, it's definitely a start,
不过她看见无数个你
except she saw a whole lot of you,
像是 到处都是
like all over the place,
同时在说话
all talking at the same time.
神马
What?
她的记忆一定是试图浮现
Her memory is definitely trying to come back.
但是
But...
我觉得我们现在应该做的
I think the best thing for us to do right now
是顺其自然
is just stay out of the way.
不 我要和她谈谈
No, I need to talk to her.
你已经在她脑中整天说个没完了
You've been talking to her all day in her head, man.
她现在应该已经烦死你了吧
I think she's kinda Nick'd out.
如果我们给她压力
I think it might actually be dangerous for her
可能会给她带来危险
if we try to push it.
你很痛苦
鉴于你的经历
我们需要谈谈
Juliette 我没法告诉你所有的细节
Juliette, I can't tell you how it all fits together.
你在已知与未知之间挣扎
Juliette 我没法告诉你所有的细节
Juliette, I can't tell you how it all fits together.
你在已知与未知之间挣扎
这注定要发生
It was destined to happen.
你在已知与未知之间挣扎
这注定要发生
It was destined to happen.
你的世界正在支离破碎
这注定要发生
It was destined to happen.
你的世界正在支离破碎
这里有支来复枪
There's a rifle in here.
Juliette
Juliette!
Vera 请告诉法庭当时你到底听到了什么
Now, Vera, please tell the court exactly what you heard.
我听见Nidaria女士对他大喊
I heard Mrs. Nidaria yelling for him
不要伤害她
not to hurt her.
然后你做了什么
What did you do then?
我冲进了卧室
I rushed to the bedroom.
你看见了什么
And what did you see?
我看见Nidaria先生抓着Nidaria女士
I saw Mr. Nidaria grab Mrs. Nidaria...
然后将她扔下了阳台
And throw her right off the balcony.
非常可怕
It was horrible.
谢谢 没有更多问题了
Thank you. No further questions.
早上好 Montgomery女士
Good morning, Ms. Montgomery.
你能告诉法庭你在Nidaria先生
Can you tell the court how long you've been employed
的家里做管家多久了吗
as Mr. Nidaria's housekeeper?
两年多
Just over two years.
你说你看见我的当事人抓住
You say you saw my client grab
- 她的妻子 是吗  - 是的
- his wife, is that correct? - Yes.
我当事人的证词表明
My client's sworn testimony states
他的妻子 当时歇斯底里
that his wife was... was hysterical.
尽管他做了最大努力 但仍然没能阻止她
And despite his best efforts, she through herself...
跳下阳台
Off the bedroom balcony.
现在 我想请你
Now, I ask you
再回想一次当时的情景
to go back to that moment one more time.
你听见了喊声
You heard shouting.
你跑进房间
You ran into the room.
- 别过来  - 快回屋里来
- Stay back! - Please come back inside.
Katherine 不要
Katherine, no!
我的上帝啊 不
Please, God, no.
你看见了什么
And what did you see?
我觉得
II think...
我只是想帮她
I was only trying to help her.
他曾试图去帮她
He was trying to help her.
反对
Objection.
法官大人 辩护人正在诱导证人
Your honor, the defense is leading the witness.
法官大人 我只是去确认一下
Your honor, I'm simply trying to confirm
在悲剧发生的那个晚上
what the witness actually saw
目击证人到底看见了什么
on the evening of this tragic accident.
法官大人 辩护人并不是在确认什么
Your honor, the defense isn't confirming anything.
他是在向证人暗示证词
He's suggesting testimony to the witness.
辩护人请上前
Counsel will please approach the bench.
我会让她的回答有效
I'm going to let the answer stand
以便于查清那晚到底发生了什么
in the interest of finding out what happened that night.
但是 下次请
But... Be more careful in how you phrase your questions
更小心地组织你提问时的措辞
when we proceed.
当然了 法官大人
Of course, your honor.
谢谢
Thank you.
现在休庭一小时 午休
We will take an hour lunch break
下午1点开庭
and resume at 1:00.
全体起立
All rise.
他叫做Henri Leseuer
His name is Henri Leseuer,
马赛来的一个商人
a businessman from Marseilles...
从事纺织业相关工作 与摩纳哥的基地组织有染
Working in textiles, with ties to Al-Qaeda in Morocco.
- 他在这做什么  - 根据报告
- What's he doing here? - According to the report,
他来是为了运送一个爆炸装置
he was here to deliver an explosive device
给太平洋西北部地区的某个人
to someone in the pacific northwest.
听起来很不确定嘛
That sounds a little vague.
是啊 因为这些都不是真的
Well, that's because none of it's true.
他的真名叫Aguistin Katt
His real name is Aguistin Katt,
1973年在马耳他出生
born in Malta in 1973.
他17岁时
He joined the French foreign legion
加入了法国外籍兵团
when he was just 17 years old,
军衔升的很快
rose quickly through the ranks,
然后突然消失了八年
and then abruptly disappeared for eight years
后来以一个新身份重新出现
only to resurface with a new identity
为侍卫军效力
working for the Verrat.
侍卫军是什么
What's the Verrat?
侍卫军是在1945年由皇室家族创立的
The Verrat was created by the royal families in 1945
一支防卫中队
as a protective squadron,
成员由格林生物组成 大多是猎狗
comprised of wesen, mostly hundjagers,
在二战中曾为双方效力
who served on both sides during world war ii.
那个炸弹的目标是你吗
Was that bomb meant for you?
我或者我要去见的那个人
For me or the man I was meeting with.
可能是冲着我们俩
Probably both.
好吧 你想让我们怎么进行这次的调查
All right, how do you want us to deal with this investigation?
以静制动
We don't.
我们将计就计 至少现在是这样
We let the lie be the truth, at least for the time being.
那你为什么告诉我们这些东西
Why are you telling us all this?
如果他们想继续玩下去的话
Well, because if they're willing to go to these lengths,
我们都得有所戒备
we all need to be on guard.
总比不知道的好
Good to know.
小心
Be careful.
- 你相信他吗  - 嗯
- You believe him? - Yeah.
你信任他吗
You trust him?
不知道
I don't know.
是我
Yeah?
- 嗨 你忙吗  - 怎么了
- Hey, are you busy? - Why?
你最好来一趟第六大街的法院
I think you need to get down to the courthouse on sixth.
发生什么事了
And what's the problem?
呃 没什么大事 只是一些无理取闹的证人
Oh, nothing much, just some rampant witness
- 还有干预陪审团  - 好的
- and jury tampering. - Okay.
嘿 感谢你们这么快就赶来
Hey. Thanks for getting down here so fast.
这里都快乱套了
It is going off the rails in there.
你们听说过Barry Kellogg 那个律师
You heard of Barry Kellogg, the lawyer?
他挺有名的 他正接手Nidaria的案子
He's pretty famous, handling the Nidaria case.
哦 是他在处理那件案子
Oh, he's handling it, all right.
他像个夜总会催眠师一样操纵着法庭
He's running the courtroom like a nightclub hypnotist.
你刚才说是关于操纵陪审团的事
You said something about jury tampering.
你有证据吗
You got proof?
呃 他不小心掉了一只蛤蟆
Well... He dropped a toad...
在男厕所里掉的
In the men's room.
神马
Excuse me?
我觉得他是个山羊怪
I think he's a ziegevolk.
否则还有谁会在厕所里吃蛤蟆
I mean, why else would he have a toad in the bathroom?
他到底在说啥
What the hell is he talking about?
山羊怪吃蛤蟆
A ziegevolk eats toads,
以使他们能对其它人进行神经致幻式的影响
which gives them a kind of psycho-hallucinogenic influence over people.
还记得那个在地下室囚禁女人的家伙吗
Remember that guy who caged women in his basement?
- 他也是山羊怪  - 是
- He was one? - Yeah.
不过这位不仅引诱女人
Except this guy's not just picking up women.
他操纵了整个陪审团
He's picking up an entire jury.
那你为什么在这儿
So why are you here?
因为Rosalee也在陪审团中
Because Rosalee is on the jury.
我只是想说
I'm just saying.
你们进去看看
Take a look at this deal,
就知道我说的真假了
and you tell me I'm crazy.
现在 根据你之前的证词
Now, according to your earlier testimony,
你在晚上8点15分左右
you arrived at the Nidaria residence
抵达了Nidaria的住所
at around 8:15 P.M.
你能描述一下 在你进入房子的时候
Can you please describe the defendant
被告人在做什么吗
when you entered the house?
好的
Yes.
我发现他在客厅 走来走去
I found him in his living room, pacing.
吴也被牵涉进这个案子
Wu's on this case?
是的 他是第一个到达案发现场的
Yeah, he was first at the scene.
吴碰到这种事的次数都快数不过来了 没有律师能够收买他
Wu's done this a million times. No lawyer's gonna trick him.
好吧
Okay.
他说什么了吗
Did he say anything?
没有
No.
Nidaria先生 我要问你几个问题
Mr. Nidaria, I need to ask you a few questions.
Nidaria先生
Mr. Nidaria.
他拒绝回答任何问题
He refused to say anything.
只说 他已经叫律师过来了
Except that he'd already called his lawyer.
被告对他妻子的遭遇
Did the defendant express any remorse
表示过任何同情吗
about what happened to his wife?
不 没有 至少在我面前是没有的
No. No, not to me.
警官 谢谢你的配合
Thank you, officer.
你可以发问了
Your witness.
警官 请允许我
Let me just say, sergeant, that...
表达对你们警局辛勤工作的感激
...we appreciate the hard work of the police department.
我们非常理解 每次在面对罪案
We understand the pressure you're under
发生时你们的压力非常大
every time you face a crime scene.
经常要面对死亡 这并不是件容易的事
It's not easy facing death on a regular basis.
你作证说 我的委托人
You testified that my client
并没有表现出任何同情
failed to express remorse...
这在我听来
Which sounds to me
好像是 一个每天都要面对死亡的警官
like the description a police officer would've had,
所做的麻木表述
one who experiences death on a daily basis.
我希望你能再重新回顾一下案发当夜
I want you to go back to that night one more time.
我的委托人为他妻子的死而悲痛欲绝
My client was devastated by her death.
事实上 当你看到我的委托人时
My client was, in fact,
他在悲伤地流泪
in tears when you saw him.
反对
Objection.
又在主观引导证人
Leading the witness.
反对无效
Sustained.
那请你自己描述一下
Then I'll let you tell it in your own words.
警官 当夜 你究竟看到了什么
What did you see, sergeant?
Nidaria先生 我要问你几个问题
Mr. Nidaria, I need to ask you a few questions.
我试图阻止她
I tried to stop her.
上帝啊 这不是真的
God, this can't be happening.
呃
Uh, well...
当我刚发现被告的时候 他在 呃
When I first saw the defendant, he was, uh...
警官 慢慢想
take your time, sergeant.
这非常重要
This is very important.
呃
Uh...
好吧 我想 他是在
Yeah, I think he was...
哭泣
Crying.
是的 在流眼泪
我可以理解成 他悲痛欲绝吗
Would you say he was distraught?
是的 可以
Yes.
警官 非常感谢你的证词
Thank you, sergeant.
这究竟怎么回事
What the hell?
尊敬的法官 我问完了
No further questions, your honor.
我都告诉你了
I'm telling you.
就是癞蛤蟆在作祟
It's the toad.
好吧 伙伴们
Okay guys...
发生什么事了
What's going on?
所以Barry kellogg是山羊怪
So Barry Kellogg is a ziegevolk?
这就是他操纵别人的真相
That's how he wins.
我还是不能相信 吴竟然
I still can't believe he got Wu
在他的操纵下 修改了证词
to reverse his testimony.
他服用的是非常珍惜品种的癞蛤蟆
He's using some kind of rare type toad
能够极大程度上的提升山羊怪的费洛蒙
to really supercharge the ziegevolk pheromones.
他一直在蛊惑我们
He's been drugging us.
他玩弄了整个法庭
He's got the whole courtroom bamboozled.
这如此明显
It's so obvious.
我不敢相信 一开始我竟然没看出来
I can't believe I didn't see it from the beginning.
既然我们看清了对手
Now that we know what we're dealing with,
有没有什么
isn't there some sort of...
防护罩之类的
Immunity nasal spray you can make
可以不让Kellogg操纵你
to keep Kellogg from influencing you?
或许吧
Maybe.
只让Rosalee不被他影响是不够的
Just getting it into Rosalee isn't gonna do any good.
我们需要整个陪审团都认为他有罪
We'd need the whole jury to vote guilty.
能不能证明他有什么行为不当之处
Could you prove some sort of malpractice?
怎么证明 吃癞蛤蟆又不犯法
How? Eating frogs isn't illegal.
也不要试图证明
And forget trying to prove
他们有超能力 能影响整个陪审团
they have magical powers to influence a jury.
而且 这个人能让各种杀人犯逍遥法外
And besides, this guy puts killers back on the streets.
只赢这一个案子是扳不倒他的
Tanking one case isn't enough.
我们要想法阻止他 一劳永逸
We need to figure out a way to stop him for good.
我们没有多少时间了 明天就要结案了
We don't have much time. Closing arguments are tomorrow.
这儿提到了一些用火蜥蜴
Here's something about pheromone production
催生出费洛蒙
using salamanders.
不行 一定要是癞蛤蟆
No. Gotta be toads.
这儿有一些论述
This one has a lengthy treatise
是关于山羊怪的骨骼分析神马的
on ziegevolk anatomy, but...
不过看起来这个作者对
The author seems mostly interested
重组三个还是四个胃这种辩论更感兴趣
in rehashing the old "Three versus four stomachs" Debate.
- 这也值得辩论  - 是的
- That's a debate? - Oh, yeah.
等一下 这有一些关于山羊怪大脑的描述
Wait, there's something here in the ziegevolk's brain.
Geruck腺就在下丘脑下方
The geruck gland, which is below the hypothalamus,
对于山羊怪来说是非常独特的构造
is unique to the ziegevolk and is devoted solely
通过汗腺 专门控制
to regulating the release of pheromones
费洛蒙的释放
through the sweat glands.
这就是为什么他们能如此有效地利用自己的费洛蒙
That's how they utilize their pheromones so effectively.
- 关于癞蛤蟆怎么说的  - 什么都没有
- What does it say about toads? - Nothing here.
不过这很好理解了
But it's pretty obvious
当他们吃某种两栖动物时
that when they eat certain amphibians,
腺体受到强烈刺激
it super-stimulates this gland and sends the production
能够释放并加强费洛蒙的功效
and strength of the pheromone into overdrive,
所以 这就是我们的目标
so... so this is our target.
那我们要从哪儿下手呢
And how do we get to it?
我们要找到一种东西 可以中和腺体
We make a solution that neutralizes that gland,
这样就能阻止他释放费洛蒙
which will stop him from producing pheromones
吃多少癞蛤蟆也没有用
no matter how many toads he eats.
类似于费洛蒙腺体阉割吧
Sort of a pheromone vasec to me,
无论他对陪审团说什么 都没有用了
which will negate everything he's told the jury.
- 我们行动吧  - 没问题
- Well, let's do it. - Okay.
哦 天哪 不
Oh, no. Oh, no.
我们还需要一种非常难得到的材料
There's one unfortunate ingredient we need.
早就知道没那么简单了
Should've seen that coming.
- 是什么  - Barry kellogg的汗水
- What is it? - Barry Kellogg's sweat.
这尼玛我们怎么得到
How the hell do we get that?
首先 我们要找到他
First, we find him.
然后 我们让他流汗
And then we make him sweat.
我不知道 我就这么和你走了对不对
I'm not sure I should really leave with you.
选择权在你
It's up to you.
我几乎一点都不了解你
I hardly know you.
但是和我在一起 你很有安全感
But you feel safe and secure with me,
你想和我去我家
and you wanna come back to my room.
知道吗 这正是我所想的
You know what, I think I do.
我以前从来没做过这样的事
I've never done this before.
完全同意
I won't hold that against you.
那是什么
What was that?
警察
Police!
小姐 你还好吗
You okay, miss?
刚才有东西就那么跳到我们面前 我不知道那究竟是什么
Something just jumped out at us. I don't know what it was.
- 像杀人狂魔一样  - 我打电话回局里
- Some kind of maniac. - I'll call it in.
- 好吧 你叫什么名字  - Olivia Sutton
- All right, what's your name? - Olivia Sutton.
Sutton小姐 你为什么不回酒吧呆会儿呢
Why don't you get back in the bar, Ms. Sutton,
不要在街上逗留
get off the street?
- 救命  - 嗨
- Help! - Hey!
来人啊 救命
Help! Help!
救命啊
- 怎么了  - 狼人
- What's wrong? - Blutbad!
快上车
Get in the truck!
快走 走啊 快走
Go, go! Come on, come on!
怎么样了
How'd it go?
嗯 他果然流汗了
Oh, he's sweating.
但是我感觉我的腹股沟拉伤了
But I think I pulled a groin muscle.
他就这么凭空出现了
He just came outta nowhere!
是的 我看到了
Yeah, yeah, I can see that.
你出了好多汗
Here, you built up quite a sweat.
哦 谢谢你 亲爱的朋友
Oh, thank you, my friend.
你真是救了我一命
You quite literally saved my life.
嗯 算不上什么
Ah, it's... it's really nothing.
- 我们就是这样的  - 是啊
- That's what wesen are for. - Yeah.
互相帮助
Helping each other, you know,
离别的格林生物远一点
get away from other wesen.
让我请你喝一杯 这是我该做的
Let me buy you a drink, it's the least I can do.
我要回家了 妻子最大 你懂的
I gotta get home. The wife and all, you know.
非常感谢你
Thank you so much.
- 没什么  - 真的很感谢
- Yeah. Sure. - Really.
呃 我的 手帕
Oh, uh, my, uh... my handkerchief?
呃 是的
Yeah.
都脏了 让我再给你买些新的吧 印名字的那种
This thing's a mess. Let me buy you a dozen more. Monogrammed.
不 不用 我就要那条
No, no, I need that one!
我的意思是 那是妻子
I mean, uh, my wife gave it to me
去年圣诞 送给我的生日礼物
as a birthday present last Christmas.
我的生日在圣诞节
My birthday's on Christmas.
就像耶稣也是圣诞过生日一样 谢谢
Like Jesus. Thanks.
我拿到了
I got it!
拿到了 他想要回去
I got it. He wanted to take it back.
但是我搞定了
But I got it.
好了 快点 我们把这个放进药罐里
Okay, hurry. Let's put it in the pot.
好了
Okay.
这还需要浸泡几个小时
This needs to steep for a few hours.
所以 我们已经拿到了他的汗液
So we leach out all his sweat.
然后 把还原剂加到药水里
Then, we add the reduction to the rest of the potion.
- 这就到了最难的部分了  - 什么
- Then comes the hard part. - Hard part?
我们不是刚刚把最难的部分完成了吗
Didn't we just do the hard part?
刚刚做的一切是帮我们制作解药
All this does is help us make the antidote.
但是我们要在Kellogg吃癞蛤蟆前把它加进去
Which we have to get into Kellogg's toad before he eats it.
这样 解药才会直接进入他的Geruck腺
That way, it'll go straight to his geruck gland.
哦 好吧 我懂了 很合理
Uh, okay. I guess that makes sense.
但我们怎么把它加进去呢
But how do we get it into his toad?
- Kellogg先生  - 是的
- Mr. Kellogg. - Yes?
我是Burkhardt警探 这是Griffin警探
I'm Detective Burkhardt. This is Detective Griffin.
我们能进去吗
May we come in?
- 出什么事了  - 我们接到
- What's this all about? - We're just following up
Olivia Sutton小姐的报警电话
on the 911 call made by Olivia Sutton.
他说 昨晚遇袭的时候是和你在一起
She said she was with you when you were attacked last night.
- 几分钟时间就够了  - 好吧 不过请快点
- It'll just take a few minutes. - All right, but make it quick.
我有个案子45分钟后就开庭了
I'm due in court in 45 minutes.
我们只做了一剂量的药水
We have just enough for one dose.
确保你把它都注射进癞蛤蟆里
Make sure you inject all of it into the toad.
- 好吧  - 或许我该来做这件事
- Okay. - Maybe I should do it?
不 不行 你现在该去法庭了
No, no. You can't. You have to be in court.
而且 如果他看见你 会认出来的
Besides, if he sees you, he'll recognize you.
我来搞定
I got it.
没问题
I'm good.
你能描述一下袭击者的长相吗
Could you describe the man who attacked you?
其实 也算不上是袭击
Well, it wasn't exactly an attack.
我可能也有点反应过度了
I may have overreacted.
那位年轻的小姐没有受伤 还是让我很欣慰的
I'm just relieved the young lady was not injured.
呃 那位小姐说你逃跑了
Uh, the woman said you ran away
- 他追着你  - 当然
- and he ran after you. - Of course.
我试图从她身边把他引开
I was trying to lead him away from her.
所以你为了她的安全着想才跑开的
So you ran away in concern for her safety.
当然 你不会这么做吗
Absolutely. Wouldn't you?
她说袭击者看上去很奇怪
Now, she said to you he looked strange,
好像他的脸和别人有些不一样
like there was something wrong with his face.
额 他穿着个帽衫 我看不清他的脸
Eh, he was wearing a hoodie. I didn't get a good look.
- 帽衫是什么颜色的  - 我不太记得了
- What color hoodie?  - I'm not sure.
- 我真的要  - 还有几个问题
- Look, I really have to...  - just a few more questions.
两只蛤蟆
Two toads?
两只蛤蟆 一剂解药
Two toads... One dose.
坑爹的吧
Seriously?
好吧 Kellogg先生
Now, Mr. Kellogg,
你是如何躲过这次袭击的
how did you get away from the attacker?
我看见一个工人正在装货
I saw a workman loading his truck.
如果没有他 我可能逃不过此劫
If it wasn't for him, I probably wouldn't have gotten away.
那个工人看到袭击者吗
Did he see the man who was chasing you?
- 是的  - 你知道他是谁吗
- Yes. - Do you know his name?
不知道
No.
工人把你载到什么地方
Where did he drive you?
回到这里酒店
Back here to the hotel.
把我载到什么地方你们也要知道吗
What does it matter where he drove me?
千万别动
Don't move.
我们只是想找到一个可以
We're trying to identify the man
辨认袭击者的证人
who can identify the man who chased you.
- 你刚才说那个工人看到袭击者了  - 他是看见了
- You said he saw him. - He did.
哎呀 不要
Oh, no.
再见面 你还能认出他吗
Would you recognize him if you saw him again?
你是说袭击者吗
The man who was chasing me?
不是 那个载你到这的人
No, the man who drove you here.
我不知道 可能吧 我不知道他是谁
I don't know, maybe. I don't know who he is.
- 那个袭击者  - 不是 那个帮我的工人
- The man who was chasing you. - No, the other man!
你知道的 我是辩护律师
Look, I'm a defense attorney.
不凑巧 我现在正在处理一个非常重要的案件
I happen to be involved in a very important case right now.
警察先生 我必须走了
Gentlemen, I have to go.
- 等一下 先生 等一下  - Kellogg先生
- No, sir, no! Nope. - Mr. Kellogg.
袭击你的人还在外面晃荡呢
There's a very dangerous man out there.
不要碰我
You're touching me.
我必须尽我们所能
We need to do everything in our power
抓到袭击者
to get him off the streets.
在你遇袭的街区我们已经接到很多投诉了
Now, we've heard other complaints in the same area.
这些袭击和你描述的很相似
Attacks just like the one you've described.
如果同样的袭击者再次犯案攻击了其他人
How would you feel if the same man
你会作何感想
attacked someone else?
我知道的是 你们在我住的酒店里
All I know is you're not gonna catch him
是抓不到犯人的
in my hotel room.
我要出庭了 我要走了
Now, I am due in court, and I am leaving...
除非你们能对法官解释
Unless you would like to explain to the judge
为什么我不能到法庭做结案陈词
why I'm not there for closing arguments.
我想我们问得差不多了
I think we're good here.
谢谢你的合作 先生
Thank you for your time, sir.
你们在这呢
There you are!
我们遇到麻烦了
We got a problem.
- 什么麻烦  - 他有两个蛤蟆
- What? - He had two toads.
- 两个蛤蟆  - 我不知道他会用哪个做午餐
- Two toads? - I don't know which one he's gonna choose
那你怎么办的
What did you do?
我能怎么做 只选一只啊
The only thing I could do. I picked one.
陪审团的各位先生们女士们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
我的家乡有句俗语
we have a saying back where I'm from.
"人不可貌相 海水不可斗量"
"Never judge a heifer by its hide."
当我站在此处
I'm reminded of these words as I stand here
恳请各位审判我的当事人时
asking you to judge my client
我再次想起了这句话
as you would a heifer.
不要只看表面 要看到本质
Not by its hide, but by its character.
Don爱Katherine胜过爱自己的生命
Don loved Katherine more than life itself.
他们一起渡过了五个多月的
They lived together in wedded bliss
幸福婚姻时光
for more than five months.
他为她不惜做任何事情
He would've done anything for her.
任何事情 但绝不会伤害她
Anything but kill her.
他的女仆
You heard testimony from his maid,
司机 厨子
chauffeur, cook,
甚至警察
even the police.
都证实了这一事实
And they all tell the same story.
一个默默无闻
The story of a quiet,
正直高尚 遵纪守法的公民
upstanding, law-abiding citizen
被我们所谓英明的司法系统
caught in the clutches of a uncaring judicial system
无辜地指控了
intent upon prosecuting an innocent man.
亲爱的朋友们  这个人的命运掌握在你们手中
My friends, the fate of this man is in your hands.
公正与否 取决于你们的决定
It's up to you to see that justice is done.
谢谢
Thank you.
阁下 Schade小姐
Mein herr, Fraulein Schade.
Eric 欢迎回来
Eric, welcome back.
你看起真是棒极了
You look fabulous.
你也是
So do you.
最好带回了那把钥匙
Which brings us to the key.
我没有那把钥匙
I don't have it.
噢 真是太令人失望了
Well, that's disappointing.
我猜你告诉我弟弟
I assume you told my brother
如果你没有拿到钥匙会发生什么
what would happen if you didn't produce it.
我说过如果他不交出钥匙 你会向那个格林和盘托出所有的事情
I told him you would tell the Grimm everything if he didn't.
我好奇他在耍什么把戏呢
I wonder what game he's playing.
他说他没有办法拿到钥匙
He said he couldn't get the key.
至少 在你给他的这么短时间内他拿不到
At least, not in the short amount of time that you gave him.
我不认为时间是个问题
I don't believe time was the issue.
动机才是问题
It's the motivation.
我不敢说我能完全理解
I can't say I completely understand
你弟弟的动机是什么
what motivates your brother.
他比其他人都要难以捉摸
He's more complicated than most men.
带点儿女巫血统他就为所欲为了
A little bit of hexenbiest goes a long way.
那个格林迟早都会
I suppose it's about time the
知道我们兄弟间的事情
Grimm knew the truth about my brother and me.
你要我告诉他吗
Do you want me to tell him?
嗯 不
Mm, no.
我已经有很长一段时间没见到我弟弟了
It's been a long time since I've seen my brother.
我很想给他一个拥抱
I'm looking forward to wrapping my arms around him.
怎么了
What?
你有些变化
What's different about you?
没有啊 为什么这样说
Nothing. Why?
我不知道 你有些
I don't know. You have this...
光彩夺目
Glow.
那是因为和你在一起
That's 'cause I'm with you.
- 你说这个要多长时间  - 很难说
- How long you think this will take? - It's hard to say.
哥一定要你说个时间 要多久呢
Well, if you had to say, how long would it take?
如果他们有罪 时间可能长点
If they're guilty, it could take forever.
如果他们无罪 通常都非常快
If they're innocent, it's usually faster.
判决已经出来了 陪审团已经回到法庭了
They've reached a verdict. Jury's coming back in.
嗷 天哪 我挑错蛤蟆了
Aw, God. I picked the wrong toad.
- 这很快啊  - 一直都是
-That was fast.  - Always is.
陪审团的各位先生们女士们
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
你们已经得出判决结果吗
have you reached a verdict?
是的 法官大人
We have, your honor.
我可以看看判决结果吗
May I see the verdict?
被告请起立
Will the defendant please rise?
Foreman女士
Madame Foreman,
请你宣读判决结果
will you please read the verdict?
俄勒冈州公民
In the case of the people of Oregon
控告Donald Nidaria
versus Donald Nidaria
一级谋杀
on the charge of murder in the first degree,
陪审团认为罪名
we find the defendant Donald Nidaria
成立
guilty.
太棒了
Yes!
这是他妈什么情况
What the hell happened?
肃静 肃静
Quiet! Quiet in the court, please.
我想要谢谢大家
I wanna thank all of you.
如果没有你们的努力
If it wasn't for what you did,
我可能就让凶手逍遥法外了
I'd be part of setting a killer free.
然后我们救了几条人命 Nidaria进了监狱
And we saved some lives. Nidaria's in jail.
Kellogg也没办法再在陪审团面前
And Kellogg will never be able to step in front of a jury again
施展他的魔力了
without antagonizing them.
我现在都无法相信 我真真实实地偷了一个人的汗液
I still can't believe I actually stole a guy's sweat.
干杯
Cheers.
哥来搞定
I got it.
抱歉 嗯 实际上我们要打烊了
I'm sorry, um, we're actually closed right now.
我只是忘记把牌子翻过来
I just... I forgot to turn the...
我需要帮助
I need help.
有人告诉我这个地方可以帮我
I was told this is the place I should come.
你看 如果你可以在其他的时间来的话
You know, if you come another time,
- 明天怎么样 我  - 我现在就需要帮助
- maybe tomorrow, I... - I need help now!
- 知道我的意思了吧  - 是滴
- See what I'm getting at? - I do.
不知道怎么回事
Something's happened to me.
我失去了我的魔力
I've lost my... Abilities.
- Monroe 一切都好吗  - 交给我吧
- Monroe, everything okay? - I got this!
- 你可以  - 你
- You should... - You!
你是陪审团的一员 是你在我身上动了手脚
You were on the jury. You did something to me.
- 你一定搞错了  - 你对我下毒
- I'm sure you're mistaken. - You poisoned me.
是你做的 你把我毁了
You did this. You ruined me!
- 我要杀了你  - 不要
- I'll kill you! - No!
Monroe
Monroe!
你
You!
你就是那个袭击者
You're the one who chased me.
他攻击Rosalee
He attacked Rosalee.
所以说 你刚刚救了这个混蛋的命
So you basically just saved this guy's life.
哦 上帝啊 谢谢你 Monroe
Oh, my God. Monroe, thank you.
还有你 你是那个警察
You! You're the cop.
- 还有你  - 怎么了
- And you! - Hey, what's going on?
哦 嘿
Oh. Hi.
你好阿
How you doing?
你们 你们所有人
All of you! You...
你们计划陷害我
you all did this to me.
在法庭上要拿出证据可有点难度
Gonna be tough to prove in court.
你因袭击别人被捕
You're under arrest for assault.
你所说的一切
Anything you say can and will
将会作为呈堂证供
be used against you in a court of law.
我要找律师
I wanna talk to my lawyer.
要是我的话就不费那心了
I wouldn't bother.
让律师都去死吧
Lawyers aren't worth a damn in here.
他说他认识几个来自莱茵贝克的人
He said he knew someone from Rhinebeck.
我觉得我不能活着回来了
I don't think I would have survived.
嘿 我的刮胡膏用完了
Hey, I'm out of shaving cream.
你下次回家能带点给我吗
Did you remember to bring any home on the way?
没事 我用你的好了
Never mind. I'll just use yours.
就快好了
Almost there.
我为你写了首歌
So I wrote you a song.
写得不好
And it is very bad.
但是我还是打算弹给你听
But I'm gonna play it anyway.
Hank打电话过来
That was Hank.
Hawthorne的东南区发生了两起谋杀案
Double homicide on southeast hawthorne.
你看见我的绿色毛衣了吗 我今天回家可能会很晚
Have you seen my green sweater? It's gonna be a very late night.
不用等我了 找到了 这件有扣子的衣服
Don't wait up. Yeah, the one with the buttons.
嘿 我的刮胡膏用完了
Hey, I'm out of shaving cream.
不要 我不喜欢红色的
No, I hate the red one.
没事 我用你的好了
Never mind, I'll just use yours.
我为你写了首歌
I wrote you a song.
刚才是Hank 我爱你
That was Hank. I love you.
hawthorne的东南区发生了两起谋杀案
Double homicide on southeast hawthorne.
不是因为我想和你上床
And... Not just because I wanna sleep with you...
想要宝宝 不过
...to want to have babies, but...
嘿嘿嘿 我只是开玩笑 别当真
Hey, hey! I'm k... I'm kidding, okay?
嘿 我的刮胡膏用完了
Hey, I'm out of shaving cream.
== 格林 第二季第17集 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献
== 翻译&时间轴：云云 暮暮 特特 嘿嘿 校对：天之行者 蜜蜜==
== 统筹：尧之雪 后期：飞在果壳里 封装：BG-Sandman ==
本字幕仅用于学习交流之用
禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
【H-SGDK】字幕组欢迎各位加入
有意者请加QQ群109164858，注明 字幕组+申请职位即可
== 格林 第二季第17集 完 ==
【H-SGDK】字幕组倾情奉献
多谢你过来
这当然要 亲
我一直等着你的来电
所以 你在经历一些难以解释的怪事
我也不知道能期待你为我干什么 但是
你有种看破这种事的能力
我能感受到
这对你是种异常的经历
我开始恢复记忆
你先前失去的记忆
我真假难辨
记忆都涌出来
你正身处两个世界的交界处
黑暗与光明
你的经历只是个开始